Elliot Connors is a formerly depressed writer from the Rust Belt, a formerly depressed region that, much like Elliot, has enjoyed something of a renaissance in recent years. His prose has been honored or featured in the Best American Essays of 2021, the Adroit Journal, the Yale Literary Magazine, McSweeney's Internet Tendency, and the Yale Record, the world's oldest humor publication, of which he was Editor in Chief. At Yale, he studied under Susan Choi, Anne Fadiman, and Mark Oppenheimer. In 2019, he received a Richter Fellowship to live in rural Québec and research the curse a priest put on his family that caused 5 of his relatives to commit suicide. He is currently working on a memoir about that experience, as well as developing several television pilots and assisting an acclaimed screenwriter (the creator of "How I Met Your Mother") with his wide-ranging portfolio. Beyond writing, Elliot has worked as a quantitative researcher for All'Trails, the New York Times and the Vera Institute of Justice.

Live-Action Half-Hour Comedy

Selected Stage and Screenwriting

Seed

<u></u>		
Mark and the Metaverse	Animated Half-Hour Comedy	2023
Bethesda Friends and Lovers	Live-Action Hour Mystery Comedy	2023
Whose Life	Live-Action Half-Hour Comedy	2022
In Lieu of Flowers	Live-Action Half-Hour Comedy	2021
How I Met Your Mother	Live-Action Half-Hour Spec	2021
McDonald's, Milkman, Stallions	Stage Sketches	2020
Selected Prose		
Prone "Notable Essay" in the Best American Essays of 2021, Adroit Prize Finalist		2021
A Curse and a Blessing: Unearthing My Family's History of Suicide in Québec Richter Fellowship		2021
Just for Teens Issue, Letter from the Editor The Yale Record		2019
In Memoriam/Fuck 'Til You Drop Issue, Letter from the Editor The Yale Record		2019
Flat Earth Issue, Letter from the Editor The Yale Record		2019
Sponsored Issue, Letter from the Editor The Yale Record		2019
The Thirteen Raddest Things About Turning 13! McSweeney's Internet Tendency		2017
Work Experience		

Work Experience

Bays Thomas Productions | Personal Assistant | New York, NY Aug. 2022 – Present Personal assistant to the creator of "How I Met Your Mother."

AllTrails | Senior Data Analyst | San Francisco, CA (Remote) Oct. 2023 – Present 2023 Apple App of the Year winner.

The New York Times | Senior Data Analyst | New York, NY Oct. 2021 – Oct. 2023 2022 Publisher's Award winner for my work launching an international version of our homepage.

Education

Yale University | B.A. English Literature, Computer Science certificate, cum laude (3.87) May 2020 Honors: Distinction in the major; Richter Fellowship for senior thesis research; published in Yale Lit Magazine Activities: Editor in Chief of the Yale Record, Co-President of the Yale Undergraduate Jazz Collective, First-Year Outdoor Orientation Leader, Tutor for Integrated Immigration and Refugee Services, Fifth Humor Sketch Comedy

Skills: Python, R, SQL, Git, GCP, AWS, dbt, Java, InDesign, Premiere Pro, Excel

Language: French

2024